<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView6"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="611dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="20dp"

        android:layout_marginTop="60dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="10dp"
        android:text="1. What are all the modes of payment available while adding transaction?\n
A. There are three different modes of payment available and those are Online Banking, Cash, and Card.\n\n

2. Can I add my own Custom Category while adding an expense?\n
A. Yes. There is field available for adding custom category in the drop-down list.\n\n

3. Is the data that I am entering in the application secure?\n
A. Yes. As you'll be needed to create an account before you use the application, the account is secure with the personal data.\n\n

4. Can I filter my data for a period of time?\n
A. No. Right now you can filter data only per day wise. This feature will be modified in future.\n\n

5. Can I add my financial goal in the application?\n
A. No. This will be integrated in future.\n\n

6. How the currency conversion works?
A. The default currency for this application is dollar. When the user selects different currency then automatic conversion takes place at the backend.\n\n
7. How recursion featrures works.\n
A. When the user marks certain transaction as recursive then that transaction is stored in the Recursion transaction. By clicking on this transaction and selecting new date, the user can regenerate transaction\n\n
8. What is the pie-chart representing?\n
A. It shows the spending in specific categories. "
        android:textStyle="bold"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView7"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="76dp"
        android:text="Frequently Asked Questions"
        android:textSize="24sp"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />\n\n
        android:textSize="18sp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>